bookmarkconnect.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy | BookmarkConnect Social Bookmarking

Our Privacy Policy

We uphold your privacy to the highest degree. A review of our privacy measures are supplied below and your information will be kept upmost confidential and secure. A review of the log files, web cookies, beacons, links, and advertisers are listed.

Log Files

Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Web Cookies and Beacons Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user. Web beacons are objects that are embedded in a webpage or email that are invisible to the user, but allow checking that a user has viewed the page or email. Other names are web bug, tracking bug, tag or page tag. This website does use cookies. Additionally, some advertisers listed on this site may use cookies and web beacons as well. This site has no access to, or control of advertisers' web cookies or web beacons. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Please check your browser's help section for instructions on how to do this.

Links

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. I encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy policy (or privacy statement) of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

Advertisers

We use outside advertising networks and companies in order to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons in order to collect data in the ad serving process. These such cookies and/or web beacons are collected by the companies and/or advertising networks, themselves. I do not have any access to this information.

Webmaster Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the BookmarkConnect.com privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at im@thrilledmedia.com
